I've been interested in third-party
Beyblade accessories for quite a while
now, but I never got around to getting
any until now. However, they really are
a bit of a mixed bag, so if you are
considering getting any of these
accessories, you should watch this
first.
>> You will visit jesterino.com
for the latest and greatest Beyblade
products.
>> Because in this video, I'll be reviewing
some of the top unofficial accessories
currently available for Beyblade X.
Starting off with slip grips. These
string launcher attachments are pretty
well regarded in the community. I
personally struggle with the string
launcher in general, even though they
are a lot of fun. I'm hypermobile and as
such, my limbs can come out of place if
I so much as look at them funny, which
means I can't put my whole body into a
string launch without doing some serious
friendly fire damage to myself. So, when
I tell you that these make all the
difference, believe me because it's
honestly hard to imagine using a string
launcher without them now. As even if
they don't directly improve your game,
it's nice not having to worry about
accidentally wrenching the string
launcher to pieces every time you shoot.
And I don't have too much more to say
about these. I still probably wouldn't
use a string launcher over a rip cord
because as I mentioned, I have the limbs
of a squid. So, that is just down to my
personal preference. My advice is if you
do use a string launcher or would like
to, these are definitely a worthwhile
investment. And I decided not to go for
the double string launcher link as I
mentioned about my issues with the
string launcher. Trying to use two of
them at once just sounded like a recipe
for disaster for me personally. However,
I did get one of the double rip cord
launcher links, which is pretty handy to
be able to launch both bays at exactly
the same time, but it's not really going
to improve your blading ability at all.
It's more just if you want to have a
mindless battle between two blades. It's
fun and handy to use, but in my opinion,
it doesn't accurately simulate what a
proper battle is really like. So, don't
go making assumptions on combo power
scalings based on the results from using
this device. And also, keep in mind, if
you are thinking of getting one, that
these only work with the shorter looped
rip cords, and though you can get
attachments to convert the longer style
rip cords into looped ones, I don't
really vibe with these kind of rip
cords, so I'm not in any rush to be
buying more accessories that I won't
want to use. And the side-by-side
launcher links are fine, but they do
often lead to the Beys hitting in midair
and even bursting before they make
contact with the stadium. And there's
not a lot of nuance with these battles,
you are basically either doing both of
them flat launch or both of them at the
same angle till every single battle.
However, I did get my hands on some
angled launcher links. This multi-pack
contains a series of clips that allow
you to connect multiple launchers
together at different angles, as well as
a double rip cord link. And like a lot
of these accessories, they are kind of
delicate and feel pretty tight to get on
and off, but that aside, being able to
load up two Beys at once is definitely
convenient, and I would say that, even
though it's less flashy than most of the
other accessories on this list, it's one
of the ones I would recommend getting
the most if you're into solo play. They
come in angles of 15, 30, 45, and 60°
though, I personally wouldn't use
anything higher than the 30° angled
connector. And to be honest, I feel that
the 45°
angles are just there to pad out what
you get, which isn't a bad thing, and
maybe there's some niche uses for them,
but in general, I'll be sticking to the
15° and 30° connectors, because they
feel pretty flimsy when all linked up
anyway, and it's easy for the Beys to
drop off pre-launch, even on the smaller
angles. So, they're a cool idea, but in
reality, they just don't really work
that well. And again, it's important to
to that these are more for fun battles
playing solo and aren't tools for
improving your blading ability or
seriously testing out competitive combos
as it's too cumbersome to be able to use
any real tactics with beyond just
pointing and shooting. However, I will
say that where these connectors really
excel is letting you put two attack or
balance types against each other without
worrying about the stamina drain or
self-pocketing of launching them
individually. So, if you're looking for
some dumb fun solo action, give them a
go, but that's all you'll really get out
of them. They also do make these triple
launcher connectors, but launching two
Beys at once can be chaotic enough as it
is. So, unless you're entirely committed
to only ever using the wide stadium on
your own, I really can't see these
getting any real use. And I also didn't
get the longer rip cord accessory as
it's not really a tactical accessory.
It's not going to make you a better
blader. It's literally just there to
make your Beys spin faster and hit
harder, and that's ultimately why I
didn't bother to get one because
Beyblade is already a high-impact game
and as such, there's notable wear and
tear on parts and even the stadium at
the speeds they usually go. So, if you
absolutely don't care about breaking
your blades and just want the ultimate
smash, go for it. Why not? Just be
careful, of course, and just remember
that beyond making your blades spin
really fast, it's a bit of a one-trick
gimmick. And I also grabbed a laser
target. This was by far the hardest to
assemble as you have to push out the
battery pack, which is very tight, bend
the thin plastic tabs around to clip it
on and off and on again if you forget to
put the grip on like I did. But, it's
one of the most tactical accessories in
theory, but in reality, I really don't
find it all that useful as much as I
wanted to because you can launch as much
as you like with the laser in the exact
same spot and it will be different each
and every time due to the minute hand
movement and differences in launch
power. You might get a little use from
this if you're just starting out or you
find yourself really struggling to
launch correctly. But as I'll elaborate
on a little bit later in the video, it's
a bit of a crutch that you really don't
need. Also, you got to be careful with
this thing as you do with any laser
because it's not a toy and you could do
some serious damage to your own or
someone else's eyesight. I did notice a
couple of instances where I wasn't
paying attention after a launch and
ended up nearly blinding myself with it.
And look, I know I'm a big silly, but
also, it's really easy to do. So, uh
just be mindful of that fact that there
is a freaking laser beam coming out of
your freaking launcher. And I also got
one of each of the launcher levels to
test out as these are another popular
tool in the community. Although
personally, I didn't feel them to be
that useful at all. The top one is
easier to see and can be used in
addition to the launcher links, but not
with other accessories like the battle
pass. Whereas the side one is a bit more
obscure and harder to see, but it can be
used with the battle pass. And in
general, the spirit levels run into the
same problems as the laser as they only
give you a fraction of the information
about your launch and if anything, end
up being a bit more of a distraction
than a useful metric to try and improve
your launch with. I'm not saying that
you won't get any use out of them.
They're interesting toys to play around
with and if you're having a massive
issue with launching, they might be
worth a try, but I really don't think
they're an essential attachment in the
long run because as a blader, you've got
to pay attention to a lot of different
things at once. Not only how you're
launching, but what your opponent is
doing as well. So, keeping your eyes on
a tiny bubble or laser crosshairs just
isn't practical. Maybe if you have the
steady hands of a surgeon, then it
wouldn't be an issue. But I'm not a
surgeon. I'm a YouTube clown who plays
with spinning tops. Also, the more you
practice with your combos, the more
you'll get a feel for how they perform,
and eventually, it will feel more
natural to you as you develop muscle
memory. So, I'll be hesitant to build a
reliance on tools like these, as you
never know if an event will allow them
or not, and if they don't, then you'll
be at a disadvantage to everyone else,
not just from the lack of being able to
use them, but also because your launcher
will then have a different weight
distribution and feel to it without
them. Ultimately, as cool as these
accessories look, I don't really think
they're practical tools to help improve
your blading, with maybe the exception
of the slip grip. And it's important to
remember that there's plenty of
top-level players who got where they are
without these tools, because they're not
essential, which is not to say that you
personally won't get any use out of
them. If you like them and feel they
might help, or you just want some fun
ways to change up how you play, go
ahead. But, if you're on the fence about
them, don't feel like you're missing out
and be at a disadvantage by not getting
them, because like with many aspects of
Beyblade, it really just boils down to
what your personal preference is. But,
those were my opinions on the top
accessories you can currently get for
Beyblade X. All in all, having been
really looking forward to using these
for ages, I was quite disappointed by a
lot of them in how they actually
perform. Although there's definitely
some fun and useful stuff available, I'm
just pretty underwhelmed by the results
personally. But, I'm sure I've missed
something off, so if I have, do let me
know, and also, please drop your honest
thoughts on these attachments down in
the comments. Hit that like button,
subscribe if you haven't already, and
I'll see you next time.